let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a keyword?",
    answer: "use strict",
    options: [
      "with",
      "if",
      "debugger",
      "use strict"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following is not considered as “statement” in the JavaScript?",
    answer: "use strict",
    options: [
      "with",
      "if",
      "debugger",
      "use strict"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
    answer: "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
    options: [
      "block that contains a single statement",
      "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
      "Conditional block",
      "both conditional block and a single statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is",
    answer: "object",
    options: [
      "string",
      "undefined",
      "boolean",
      "object"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one of the following is a ternary operator?",
    answer: "?",
    options: [
      "+",
      "?",
      ":",
      "–"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which one of the following is also known as Conditional Expression?",
    answer: "immediate if",
    options: [
      "Switch statement",
      "Alternative to if-else",
      "If-then-else statement",
      "immediate if"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "==",
      "!==",
      "!",
      "&&"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "“An expression that can legally appear on the left side of an assignment expression.” is a well known explanation for variables, properties of objects, and elements of arrays. They are called",
    answer: "Lvalue",
    options: [
      "Prototypes",
      "Properties",
      "Definition",
      "Lvalue"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What will we get if we compare “one” with “8” using the less than operator (“one”<8)?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "NaN",
      "True",
      "False",
      "Undefined"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which type of JavaScript language is it?",
    answer: "High-level",
    options: [
      "Object-Based",
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Assembly-language",
      "High-level"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
    answer: "The local element"
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
    answer: "Function/Method"
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following types of a variable is volatile?",
    answer: "Volatile variable"
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
    answer: "Both 0x and 0X"
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints______.",
    answer: "Displays 'Infinity'"
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "In JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error?",
    answer: "Division by zero"
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which of the following given functions of the Number Object formats a number with a different number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
    answer: "toFixed()"
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
    answer: "valueOf()"
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters?",
    answer: "substr()"
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "In JavaScript, what does x===y imply?",
    answer: "Both are equal in the value and data type."
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable 'a' is not equal to 'NULL':",
    answer: "if(a!==null)"
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Suppose we have a text 'human' that we want to convert into a string without using the 'new' operator. Which is the correct way from the following to do so:",
    answer: "String(human)"
  }  
  ];
  